Guide to the Ruth Ann Overbeck papers & Washington Perspectives, Inc. records, 1663-2007 MS2032
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Research materials, 1663-2007; MS2032 Series 6; 18.5 Linear feet
  - Maryland: Cross Manor [5/5], 1987-1988 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Maryland: Cross Manor [1/2], 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Maryland: Cross Manor [2/2], 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Maryland: Belair Mansion, undated (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Nail and shards from Cross Manor, undated (Box SHARED Box 20, Box 69)
    These artifacts were found in a brown paper bag with a handwritten note of what they are and where they were found. The list is difficult to read, but is included in the box for researchers to decipher.
- Washington Perspectives Incorporation (W.P.I.) administration, records, 1946-1985; MS2032 Series 7; 1.25 Linear feet
  The material within this series is a sampling of the administrative workings of W.P.I. The type of material included is not inclusive to the type of material one may find produced by a small business. For example, there is a small amount of financial records and telephone logs, but no personnel records.
  - Articles of Incorporation, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Brochure Appalachian House, undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Brochure Iran Orientation Seminar, undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Brochure Executive Resources Associates (ERA), undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Brochure Take One Tour, undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1984 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence with Martin K. Gordon, undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Financial bank records, 1975-1985 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Financial sample of checks and deposit slips, 1975-1985 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Histories, undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Retna Walden Gambaro work for her (includes photos), undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Assorted small jobs, undated (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Phone Log, 1980-1981 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Phone Log, 1979-1980 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Phone Log, 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Sample invoices, undated (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Small business questionnaire, undated (Box 42, Folder 17)